[{"question": "After selecting an Amazon EC2 Dedicated Host reservation, which pricing option would provide the largest discount?", "answers": ["No upfront payment", "Hourly on-demand paymen", "Partial upfront payment", "All upfront payment"]}, {"question": "What is the purpose of AWS Storage Gateway?", "answers": ["It ensures on-premises data storage is 99.99999999% durable.", "It connects on-premises data storage to the AWS Cloud.", "It connects to multiple Amazon EC2 instances", "It transports petabytes of data to and from AWS."]}, {"question": "Which AWS service is used to provide encryption for EBS?", "answers": ["AWS Certificate Manager", "AWS Systems Manager", "AWS KMS", "AWS Config"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service enables resources to be automatically allocated to satisfy capacity requirements as traffic goes up and down?", "answers": ["Amazon EBS", "Auto Scaling", "AWS Systems Manager", "AWS Service Catalog"]}, {"question": "To use the AWS CLI, users are required to generate:", "answers": ["a managed policy", "a password policy", "an access/secret key", "an API key"]}, {"question": "An application runs on multiple Amazon EC2 instances that access a shared file system simultaneously.Which AWS Storage service should be used?", "answers": ["Amazon EFS", "Amazon EBS", "Amazon S3", "AWS Artifact"]}, {"question": "Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources? SELECT TWO", "answers": ["Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)", "AWS Lambda", "AWS CodeDeploy", "Amazon Glacier", "AWS Organizations"]}, {"question": "What will help a company perform a cost benefit analysis of migrating to the AWS Cloud?", "answers": ["AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "Cost Explorer", "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "AWS Trusted Advisor"]}, {"question": "When building a cloud Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) model, which cost elements should be considered for workloads running on AWS? (Select THREE.)", "answers": ["Compute costs", "Storage costs", "Network infrastructure costs", "Facilities costs", "Hardware lifecycle costs"]}, {"question": "Which AWS Service is used to automate configuration management using Chef and Puppet?", "answers": ["AWS Config", "AWS OpsWorks", "AWS CloudFormation", "AWS Systems Manager", "AWS Trusted Advisor"]}, {"question": "What should users do if they want to install an application in geographically isolated locations?", "answers": ["Install the application using multiple internet gateways", "Deploy the application to an Amazon VPC", "Deploy the application to multiple AWS Regions", "Configure the application using multiple NAT gateways"]}, {"question": "Which of the following are components of Amazon VPC (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["Objects", "Subnets", "Buckets", "Internet gateways", "Access/Secret Keys"]}, {"question": "What are the benefits of developing and running a new application in the AWS Cloud compared to on-premises? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["AWS automatically distributes the data globally for higher durability", "AWS makes it easy to architect for high availability", "AWS can easily accommodate application demand changes", "AWS will take care of operating the application", "AWS takes care application security patching."]}, {"question": "How can a user protect against AWS service disruptions if a natural disaster affects an entire geographic area?", "answers": ["Deploy applications across multiple Availability Zones within an AWS Region.", "Use a hybrid cloud computing deployment model within the geographic area.", "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions", "Store application artifacts using AWS Artifact and replicate them across multiple AWS Regions"]}, {"question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for configuration management?", "answers": ["It is shared between AWS and the customer.", "It is solely the responsibility of the customer.", "It is solely the responsibility of AWS.", "It is not part of the AWS shared responsibility model."]}, {"question": "Treating infrastructure as code in the AWS Cloud allows users to:", "answers": ["automate the infrastructure provisioning process.", "turn over application code to AWS so it can run on the AWS infrastructure.", "let a third party automate an audit of the AWS infrastructure.", "automate migration of on-premises hardware to AWS data centers"]}, {"question": "Within the AWS Shared responsibility model, who is responsible for security and compliance?", "answers": ["The customer is responsible.", "AWS and the customer share responsibility.", "AWS is responsible.", "AWS shares responsibility with the relevant governing body."]}, {"question": "Which AWS servic allows for effective cost management of multiple AWS accounts?", "answers": ["AWS Organizations", "AWS Trusted Advisor", "AWS Direct Connect", "Amazon Connect"]}, {"question": "AWS Trusted Advisor provides recommendations on which of the following? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["Cost Optimization", "Auditing", "Serverless architecture", "Performance", "Scalability"]}, {"question": "Which load balancer types are available with Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["F5 Big-IP and Citrix NetScaler load balancers", "Public load balancers with AWS Application Auto Scaling capabilities", "Classic Load Balancers", "Application Load Balancers", "Cross-zone load balancers with public and private IPs"]}, {"question": "A Cloud Practitioner is asked how to estimate the cost of using a new application on AWS.\u00a0What is the MOST appropriate response?", "answers": ["Use Amazon AppStream 2.0 for real-time pricing analytics.", "Inform the user that AWS pricing allows for on-demand pricing.", "Use Amazon QuickSight to analyze current spending on-premises.", "Direct the user to the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator for an estimate."]}, {"question": "Which AWS service can be used to query stored datasets directly from Amazon S3 using standard SQL?", "answers": ["AWS Glue", "Amazon Athena", "AWS Data Pipeline", "Amazon CloudSearch"]}, {"question": "Which type of AWS Storage is ephemeral and is deleted when an instance is stopped or terminated?", "answers": ["Aazon EBS", "Amazon EC2 instance store", "Amazon EFS", "Amazon S3"]}, {"question": "What is an example of high availability in the AWS Cloud?", "answers": ["Consulting AWS technical support at any time day or night", "Making any AWS service available for use by paying on demand", "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails", "Deploying in any part of the world using AWS Regions"]}, {"question": "A director has been tasked with investigating hybrid cloud architecture. The company currently accesses AWS over the public internet.Which service will facilitate private hybrid connectivity?", "answers": ["AWS Direct Connect", "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) NAT Gateway", "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) Transfer Acceleration", "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)"]}, {"question": "Which of the following can be used a second factor within the AWS Management Console for AWS Multi-Factor Authentication (AWS MFA)?", "answers": ["AWS IAM password", "U2F security key token", "Access key or secret key", "AWS Certificate Manager certificates"]}, {"question": "A customer runs an On-Demand Amazon Linux EC2 instance for 3 hours, 5 minutes and 6 seconds. For how much time will the customer be billed?READ:https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/Stop_Start.htmlhttps://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/Stop_Start.html", "answers": ["3 hours, 5 minutes", "3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds", "3 hours, 6 minutes", "4 hours"]}, {"question": "Which task requires using AWS account root user credentials?READ:https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws_tasks-that-require-root.html", "answers": ["Viewing billing information", "Changing the AWS Support plan", "Starting and stopping Amazon EC2 instances", "Opening an AWS Support case"]}, {"question": "AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["Implementing Amazon Rekognition", "Using AWS Shield-protected resources", "Blocking access with Security Groups", "Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)", "Enforcing password strength and expiration"]}, {"question": "Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Select TWO.)READ:Five pillars \u2014 operational excellence, security, reliability, performance efficiency, and cost optimization", "answers": ["Multiple Availability Zones", "Encryption usage", "Security", "Performance efficiency", "High availability"]}, {"question": "What does the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator do?", "answers": ["Compares on-premises costs to colocation environments", "Estimates monthly billing based on projected usage", "Estimates power consuption at existing data centers", "Estimates CPU utilization"]}, {"question": "What function do security groups serve related to Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance security?", "answers": ["Secure AWS user accounts with AWS Identity and Access management (AIM) policies", "Act as a virtual firewall for the Amazon EC2 instance", "Provide DDos protection with AWS Shield", "Use Amazon CloudFront to protect the Amazon EC2 instance"]}, {"question": "Which of the following can a customer use to enable single sign-on (SSO) to the AWS Console?", "answers": ["Amazon Connect", "AWS Directory Service", "Amazon Pinpoint", "Amazon Rekognition"]}, {"question": "A Cloud Practitioner needs to store data for 7 years to meet regulatory requirements.Which AWS service will meet this requirements at the lowest cost?", "answers": ["AWS Snowball", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Redshift", "Amazon S3 Glacier"]}, {"question": "Which AWS hybrid storage service enables your on-premises applications to seamlessly use AWS Cloud storage through standard file-storage protocols?", "answers": ["AWS Snowball", "AWS Storage Gateway", "AWS Direct Connect", "AWS Snowball Edge"]}, {"question": "A company with a Developer-level AWS Support plan provisioned an Amazon RDS database and cannot connect to it.Who should the developer contact for this level of support?", "answers": ["AWS Support using a support case", "AWS Professional Services", "AWS Technical Account Manager", "AWS Consulting partners"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service or feature allows a company to visualize, understand, and manage AWS costs and usage over time?", "answers": ["AWS Cost Explorer", "AWS Budgets", "AWS Organizations", "onsolidated billing"]}, {"question": "The pay-as-you-go pricing model for AWS Services:", "answers": ["Requires payment up front for AWS Services", "it is relevant only for Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, and Amazon RDS", "Reduces capital expenditures", "Reduces operational expenditures"]}, {"question": "Which of the following provides the ability to share the cost benefits of Reserved Instances across AWS accounts?", "answers": ["AWS Cost Explorer between AWS accounts", "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Reserved Instance Utilization Report", "Linked accounts and consolidated billing", "Amazon EC2 Instance Usage Report between AWS accounts"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service provides inbound and outbound network ACLs to harden external connectivity to Amazon EC2?", "answers": ["Amazon API Gateway.", "Amazon VPC", "Amazon Connect", "AWS IAM"]}, {"question": "Which services use AWS edge locations? (Select ONE.)", "answers": ["Amazon CloudFront", "Amazon RDS", "Amazon ElastiCache"]}, {"question": "When a company provisions web servers in multiple AWS Regions, what is being increased?", "answers": ["Coupling", "Availability", "Security", "Durability"]}, {"question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using AWS?READ:https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-overview.pdf", "answers": ["AWS audits user data.", "Data is automatically secure.", "There is no guessing on capacity needs.", "AWS manages compliance needs."]}, {"question": "How can a company isolate the costs of production and non-production workloads on AWS?", "answers": ["Create Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles for production and non-production workloads.", "Use different accounts for production and non-production expenses.", "Use Amazon EC2 for non-production workloads and other services for production workloads.", "Use Amazon CloudWatch to monitor the use of services."]}, {"question": "What can be used to reduce the cost of running Amazon EC2 Instances? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["Spot Instances for stateless and flexible workloads", "Reserved Instances for sustained workloads", "Memory optimized instances for high-compute workloads", "Spend limits set using AWS Budgets"]}, {"question": "How does AWS most effectively reduce computing costs for a growing start-up company?", "answers": ["It provides on-demand resources for peak usage.", "It automates customer relationship management.", "It implements a fixed monthly computing budget.", "It automates the provisioning of individual developer environments."]}, {"question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, CUSTOMER responsibilities include which one of the following?", "answers": ["Securing the hardware, software, facilities, and networks that run all products and services.", "Configuring the operating system, network, and firewall.", "Providing certificates, reports, and other documentation directly to AWS customers under NDA.", "Obtaining industry certifications and independent third-party attestations."]}, {"question": "Which of the following describes the relationships among AWS Regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations? (Select TWO)", "answers": ["There are more AWS Regions than Availability Zones.", "There are more edge locations than AWS Regions.", "An edge location is an Availability Zone.", "There are more AWS Regions than edge locations.", "There are more Availability Zones than AWS Regions."]}, {"question": "What is an advantage of deploying an application across multiple Availability Zones?", "answers": ["The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone.", "There will be better coverage as Availability Zones are geographically distant and can serve a wider area", "There will be decreased application latency that will improve the user experience.", "There is a lower risk of service failure if a natural disaster causes a service disruption in a given AWS Region"]}, {"question": "Which service enables customers to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?", "answers": ["AWS Trusted Advisor", "Amazon GuardDuty", "Amazon Inspector", "AWS Config"]}, {"question": "What are the multiple, isolated locations within an AWS Region that are connected by low-latency networks called?", "answers": ["AWS Direct Connects", "Availability Zones", "Edge locations", "Amazon VPCs"]}, {"question": "Which scenarios represent the concept of elasticity on AWS? (Choose two.)", "answers": ["Scaling the number of Amazon EC2 instances based on traffic", "Automatically directing traffic to less-utilized Amazon EC2 instances.", "Resizing Amazon RDS instances as business needs change.", "Having the ability to create and govern environments using code", "Using AWS compliance documents to accelerate the compliance process."]}, {"question": "When is it beneficial for a company to use a Spot Instance?", "answers": ["When there is flexibility in when an application needs to run.", "When there are mission-critical workloads.", "When dedicated capacity is needed.", "When an instance should not be stopped."]}, {"question": "Which statement best describes Elastic Load Balancing?", "answers": ["It translates a domain name into an IP address using DNS.", "It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances.", "It collects metrics on connected Amazon EC2 instances.", "It automatically adjusts the number of Amazon EC2 instances to support incoming traffic"]}, {"question": "Which of the following is an important architectural design principle when designing cloud applications?", "answers": ["Use multiple Availability Zones.", "Use tightly coupled components.", "Use open source software.", "Provision extra capacity."]}, {"question": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["AWS Trusted Advisor", "AWS Online Tech Talks", "AWS Blog", "AWS Forums", "AWS Classroom Training"]}, {"question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["AWS WAF", "Amazon EC2", "Amazon CloudFront", "Amazon Inspector", "I have no idea"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service can be used to generate alerts based on an estimated monthly bill?READ:https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html", "answers": ["AWS Config", "Amazon CloudWatch", "AWS X-Ray", "AWS CloudTrail"]}, {"question": "Where are AWS compliance documents, such as an SOC 1 report, located?", "answers": ["Amazon Inspector", "AWS CloudTrail", "AWS Artifact", "AWS Certificate Manager"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service provides a customized view of the health of specific AWS services that power a customers workloads running on AWS?READ:https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/personal-health-dashboard/", "answers": ["AWS Service Health Dashboard", "AWS Personal Health Dashboard", "AWS X-Ray", "Amazon CloudWatch"]}, {"question": "What does AWS Shield Standard provide?", "answers": ["WAF rules", "DDoS protection", "Data encryption"]}, {"question": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["Amazon EC2", "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)", "Amazon Aurora", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Redshift"]}, {"question": "In which scenario should Amazon EC2 Spot Instances be used?", "answers": ["A company wants to move its main website to AWS from an on-premises web server.", "A company has a number of application services whose Service Level Agreement (SLA) requires 99.999% uptime.", "A company's heavily used legacy database is currently running on-premises", "A company has a number of infrequent, interruptible jobs that are currently using On-Demand Instances"]}, {"question": "A user needs an automated security assessment report that will identify unintended network access to Amazon EC2 instances and vulnerabilities on those instances. Which AWS service will provide this assessment report?", "answers": ["AWS Config", "EC2 security groups", "Amazon Inspector", "Amazon Macie"]}, {"question": "Which disaster recovery scenario offers the lowest probability of down time?", "answers": ["Backup and restore", "Multi-site active-active", "Warm standby", "Pilot light"]}]